A man in a kitchen is looking for thing to make a coffee.
Un homme dans une cuisine cherche de quoi faire du café.
The man is frustrated about not finding what he is looking for.
L'homme est frustré de ne pas trouver ce qu'il cherche.
The man rearranges the kitchen in a time-lapse.
L'homme réorganise la cuisine en accéléré.
The man is now browsing a badly laid out pizza delivery website and is shaking his head.
L'homme navigue maintenant sur un site Web de livraison de pizzas mal conçu et secoue la tête.
A woman is using the same complex website with screen magnification.
Une femme utilise le même site Web complexe avec un agrandisseur d'écran.
She only sees a portion of the screen at a time, so the website appears even more confusing.
Elle ne voit qu'une partie de l'écran à la fois, ce qui rend le site Web encore plus confus.
The woman is shaking her head and is unable to use that website.
La femme secoue sa tête et est incapable d'utiliser le site Web.
The man calls a friend over to help.
L'homme appelle une amie pour l'aider.
The friend is just as confused and navigates to a different, better pizza website.
L'amie est tout aussi déroutée et navigue vers un meilleur site Web de pizzas.
This second website is much clearer and easier to use. They are both happy.
Ce second site Web est bien plus clair et facile d'utilisation. Tous les deux sont heureux.
The woman using screen magnification has also used that website and is delightfully eating a pizza.
La femme utilisant un agrandisseur d'écran a elle aussi utilisé ce site Web et savoure une pizza.